<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

<!--Terms of use-->
<string name="html_terms_of_use"><html><body>Last modification: November 23, 2016\n\n\nThank you for using <b>“WiFi Authority”</b>.\n\nBy using <b>“WiFi Authority”
</b> the user agrees with the following terms:\n\n1. Mobile applications, like any other piece of software are prone to fails,
bugs, crashes, data losses and other malfunctions. The operating system and the hardware on which it is running are prone to the same problems. So, <b>mohb apps</b>
is not responsible for any consequences of such malfunctions, use this application at your own risk.
\n\n2. The maps service is provided by <b>“Google Maps
<sup><small><small><small>TM</small></small></small></sup>”</b> API, so <b>mohb apps</b> is not responsible for any malfunctions
that can occur with it and any consequences of it.\n\n3. These terms
are subjected to changes. In this case, the user will be notified in the application page on <b>“Google Play Store
<sup><small><small><small>TM</small></small></small></sup>”</b> when a new version of the app has been released and
by continuing using the application the user automatically agrees with the new terms.
\n\n\n\n<small><i>“Google Maps<sup><small><small><small>TM</small></small></small></sup>” and “Google Play Store
<sup><small><small><small>TM</small></small></small></sup>” are trademarks of Google, Inc.\n\nmohb apps
does not have any partnership or any other form of relation with Google, Inc.</i></small>\n\n\n
</body></html></string>

<!--Privacy policy-->
<string name="html_privacy_policy"><html><body>Last modification: November 23, 2016\n\n\nThank you for using <b>“WiFi Authority”</b>\n\nThrough
this document, <b>mohb apps</b> guarantee that <b>“WiFi Authority”</b> does not collect any user\'s personal data necessary to the proper operation of the application,
including current location. These data are stored only on local storage of the user\'s device and it is not sent in any way to <b>mohb apps</b>.
If the user uninstall the app, all this data is permanently deleted. <b>“WiFi Authority”</b> also does not collect any other user\'s personal data, including phone identity, contacts, files,
installed applications or any other data that can identify the user. The internet connection is used only by the purpose of get the maps, get address information of the locations,
get Legal Notices, get Help pages and send feedback e-mails.\n\nThis document
is subjected to changes. In this case, the user will be notified in the application page on <b>“Google Play Store
<sup><small><small><small>TM</small></small></small></sup>”</b> when a new version of the app have been
released.\n\n\n\n<small><i>“Google Play Store
<sup><small><small><small>TM</small></small></small></sup>” is a trademark of Google, Inc.\n\n\n</i></small>
</body></html></string>

<!--Icons attribution-->
<string name="html_icons_attribution">The wifi signal representation in the application icon and the icons inside the application were designed by <b><i>Google, Inc.</i></b> under the “material design guidelines“ and used and modified according to <b>Creative Commons
Attribution 4.0 International License (CC-BY 4.0)</b>.</string>

</resources>